THE APARTMENT JOB
CANDIDATE 2, PARK HAE-KANG
Cheers.
Wait, Mr. Park. This calls for a toast.
A toast? We don't do stuff like that.
Then can I say something instead?
Fine.
That's great.
Everyone, you've all seen headlines like,
"Apartment complexes,
a hotbed of corruption!"
Not writing up contracts properly,
handing no-bid contracts
to favored companies,
inflating construction costs,
embezzling maintenance funds…
I don't want to see you guys on the news.
So please,
don't get involved in such corruption.
- I hope you finish your term
- This is boring.
without any trouble, Mr. Park.
All right, then. Cheers!
Cheers!
Why the long faces?
You made an intermittent family
and got the position you wanted so badly.
Since it's come to this,
I just wanted to encourage you,
as your fake wife, to do your best.
Come on. Cheers!
- Cheers!
How refreshing.
Out of everything I've ever done,
that was by far the hardest.
The packages were piling up
like a mountain…
What's with you? Why are you so drunk?
He had a tough time.
You have a chili flake
stuck in your teeth.
I heard the good news.
- Congratulations.
- You already heard?
Blood?
What's his deal? I'm sure that was blood.
I'm almost there.
Yong-man…
Just focus
on saving Yong-man for now.
THE APARTMENT JOB
Right. That's nonsense.
My elbow's been acting up.
I can't hit the ball well.
- Are you okay?
- Goodness.
Don't feel too upset about this, Mr. Lee.
Right now, you're not in a position
to sit at the same table as us.
It's just a tiny bump in the road.
Mr. Lee wouldn't stumble
over something so small.
That'd be embarrassing.
This is so absurd, it's almost comical.
In any case, it's no big deal,
so don't worry about it.
Eat up. You look so worn out.
Yes, sir.
Should we have gotten him beef?
For workers, pork is still best.
Even with a simple home renovation,
you run into all sorts of issues.
But we're developing an entire city.
You know,
I just don't like Oman New Town
getting mentioned like this.
I don't want this small spark
turning into some huge corruption scandal
like in the movies.
I want this wrapped up cleanly
without all that nonsense.
Wrapping things up cleanly
is my specialty, you know.
LEOPARD OF KILIMANJARO
Have you ever seen a hyena
Roaming the foothills
In search of prey?
Hyenas roam the foothills
Only searching for carrion
I want to be a leopard, not a hyena
- He's inside, right?
- Yes, he is.
How is he right now?
I wake up great, then I wake up small
Now, I'm resting
In a dark corner of the world
I can't just come like the wind
And leave like morning dew
I should leave my mark behind
I was feeling a little frustrated,
so I wanted to sing this song first.
- Mr. Yoo.
- Yes?
Didn't you conduct a cultural heritage
survey before construction started?
We did, but--
They found a bowl!
Something that shouldn't have been found!
It's bad enough that I spent my own money
digging up my own land
and discovered something
that shouldn't have been there.
- Mr. Choi.
- Yes?
How much interest
will I have to pay on my bank loan
while the construction is on hold?
Well…
It's a pretty big amount.
It's been a while.
Put your heads in position.
Sir…
Heads in position!
- Yes, sir!
- Move!
Love is lonely
Because you bet your fate on it
Lonely because you risk everything
I'm lonely.
I feel like I'm the only one doing my job.
Find a way
to resume construction immediately!
I'm sorry, sir,
but unless the relics are fake,
- there's no way to reverse this!
- Mr. Park!
Please forgive me, sir!
Fake?
What? You did what?
- A fake wife?
- Yes.
It's just like another stand-in gig.
I get that you need the money,
but have you lost your mind?
You wanted to be a lawyer.
I'm going to start studying again
once I get the remaining money.
There are only a few days left.
Does Ha-jeong know?
Of course not.
She's in France right now.
I sent her there
with the advance payment I got.
Her dream is to be a patissier,
so I told her to go and experience stuff.
But why is that guy going so far
as to fake a family to become
a residents' association president?
What?
Just think about it.
Why would he pay you that much
just for that position?
I know.
My mom's acquaintance's
in-law's cousin's friend--
Yeong-ju, that's practically a stranger.
Right. Anyway, that stranger
became an apartment president
and pocketed a huge sum.
They even got a new car
and moved to a fancy place too.
- Could he also be--
- Hey.
Mr. Park isn't that kind of person.
Why are you shouting at me?
Then what kind of man is he, exactly?
What?
Well, he's…
What is Park Hae-kang doing on my ceiling?
Let's just sleep.
- I'm here!
- Hi.
- I'm not late, am I?
- You are.
What? Is it someone's birthday?
No, but it's the first day
of our boss's term as president.
I put my skills to use
to make a hearty meal
to keep our strength up.
Mr. Park, you're drinking
espresso again without eating?
I'm fine.
It's not fine with me.
Your brothers prepared
a nice meal for you.
You should at least join them.
It's okay.
Hey.
Come on.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's seaweed soup. It's hot.
All right.
Here.
Should I feed it to you? Here.
I'll eat it myself.
This is good.
You did great.
You finally seem like an ordinary human.
Is that shaved ice?
I'll give you more.
Why are you crying?
This is the first time
you've tried my cooking.
So…
Dad.
- Yes?
Which dad?
- Me?
What is it?
Do you have something to say?
Mom.
Ms. Kang, Gyeong-buk's calling you.
I'm still not used to being called "Mom."
What is it?
It's nothing.
- I'm getting ready for work.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
It looks like
they're from every household.
Seems like everyone was desperate
for a change in leadership.
Sang-tae.
- Yes?
- Watch your mouth.
Someone could hear you. Be careful.
But we're the only ones here.
- Sorry.
- You should all lie low.
A change in leadership
always brings a bloodbath.
I wouldn't go that far…
You're all so clueless.
The blood…
What are you waiting for?
We should get ready
to welcome the new president.
Let's…
do a good job.
If you don't want that
to happen to you, okay?
Here's a gift.
The bloodbath has already begun.
Is it cold now?
It's nice and cold.
- Hold up.
- You scared me.
It's okay to drink by yourself,
but don't gamble at the senior center.
I won't.
I don't even have the money for that.
I can't.
You're someone to gamble
even if you're broke.
If the boss finds out, you're dead.
All right.
Dad.
Let me talk to your grandpa for a second.
Okay.
Ms. Kang, aren't you getting ready?
Getting ready for what?
We have to go to the management office.
What? Mr. Park's the president.
Why would we go there?
It's his first day of work.
We should go and support him.
And something might happen to him,
so we should show him
that we have his back.
Heading to work on his first day
with the support of his family…
- Wouldn't it be a beautiful sight?
- Yeah.
What do you mean by "beautiful"?
It would be weird for a grown man's
entire family to follow him to work.
But it's nothing hard to do.
You're getting paid.
You should at least
do some things that we ask.
Employees also have the right
to refuse unreasonable or unfair demands.
Unbelievable.
Neglect of duty, dereliction of duty.
That's what you're doing right now,
Ms. Kang Ha-ri.
As you may have noticed,
he went to law school.
- Gosh.
- She should know too.
Hey. Dereliction of duty
applies only to public officials.
I'm not working as a public official here.
How can you not know that?
As you may have noticed,
she also attended law school.
They should know too.
Well, you're not an employee,
to be precise.
How can you not know that?
Oh, right. You failed the bar exam.
What did you just say?
I'll support him in my own way,
so just know that.
You look nice, Mr. Park.
You've succeeded, thanks to me.
Mr. Park!
True Value State's residents' association
president, Park Hae-kang!
Good luck today!
You look so cool, Hae-kang!
Ha-ri, bring in the laundry.
I can't believe I just did that.
But did all of them know
that I failed the bar exam?
Darn it!
I'm almost there.
With the president's seal,
the facility manager's seal,
and the apartment complex bank book,
this will all be over.
Let's go.
Good morning!
Hello.
Everyone's here again.
Welcome, President Park.
Your family's here too.
- You really are…
- Hello!
a close-knit family.
- Are you busy, Mr. Choi?
- Not at all.
I was just stamping
some payroll paperwork.
Come on, Sang-tae.
Give him the thing we prepared.
- Congratulations, President Park.
- Thank you.
- It looks great on you.
I hope you like your office.
I love it, Mr. Choi.
And here.
There are some basic handover notes,
along with the bank book
and your stamp too.
I look forward to working with you, sir.
The power of the president.
Pardon?
You're always so interesting.
I'll get going then.
You have a meeting
with the contractors later,
so don't forget.
- Thank you.
- You're all so close.
- Yes.
- It's beautiful.
- It's shining.
- You did it, Boss.
- You did it.
It's not over yet, so stay sharp.
- Yes, sir.
Let's start wrapping things up.
Once we get the money
from the bank tomorrow morning,
- we're leaving immediately.
- Yes, sir.
It's a large amount.
- Gyeong-nam, prepare a bag for the cash.
- Yes, sir.
Big Guy, sell off everything in the home.
Yes, sir.
- Je-gil, get the facility manager's stamp.
- Yes, sir.
The manager…
just threw his stamp to the side
on his desk earlier.
- Leave it to me, sir.
- He's so careless.
What about the Lizard and Ms. Kang?
- You shouldn't enter.
- It's fine.
It's authorized personnel only.
I'm the one who made him the president.
What do we call that again?
Kingmaker?
Yes. I'm the kingmaker,
so of course, I'm authorized.
Don't you agree, Mr. Park?
It's fine. You can go.
Mr. Park.
This is a gift
for your new position. Here.
What is this?
Unwrap it. Go on.
Our club members all felt so grateful,
so we pitched in to get this made for you.
PRESIDENT PARK HAE-KANG
Wow, a phoenix…
Not even the President
would have a plaque like that.
The position makes the person.
You need something cool
like this right here…
to give your desk some presence.
Congratulations.
Come on, Mr. Park. Congratulations.
It's nice, isn't it?
So…
we have to find something to pick at.
We have to paint
Park Hae-kang's election as illegal.
Then what should we pick at,
and how should we play it?
Maybe we can make an issue
of his candidate registration form.
How about Park Hae-kang's photo size?
He used a larger photo than yours.
What do you think?
He did violate the rules, didn't he?
We can't solve this problem
by making an issue
of something so trivial.
Not something like that.
We need something
that can bring him down in one go.
Something critical.
Mr. Lee, you took a lot of kickbacks
from Hansong Equipment, didn't you?
And Ms. Kim.
I know you accepted a lot of money
from Director Park
during the bidding
for the kindergarten contract.
And Mr. Oh,
you pulled some strings
to get your sibling hired
at the landscaping company.
I can easily come up
with a long list of stuff like this
just by thinking for a second.
But you look much too relaxed right now.
I really…
Listen.
If we can't get rid of Park Hae-kang,
if we fail to drag him down
from that position,
we're all dead!
We're all going down.
Do you understand?
Ever heard the saying,
"Power never lasts"?
It means no one can stay in power forever.
President Park, you really are smart.
They say power cannot last ten years.
But foolish humans always grow corrupt,
thinking it will last forever.
That is why I'm offering to manage
that kind of stuff for you.
- What stuff?
- You know.
Family risk.
Politicians back then
all had family scandals.
No matter how good a politician you are,
one family scandal can bring you down.
Well, I guess so.
But that has nothing to do with us.
Of course, it does.
Power and corruption
are practically inseparable.
That is why I'm offering to become
your Senior Secretary for Civil Affairs
and manage such issues for you.
- Senior Secretary?
Yes. Senior Secretary for Civil Affairs.
Isn't that nice?
I just want to see you
for a long time, that's all.
So let me do that for you.
Okay? I'll be the Senior Secretary
for Civil Affairs.
Are you ready, sir?
- You're here too, Ms. Jang.
- Yes, Mr. Choi.
President Park,
are you ready?
Let's go!
Will it be okay to leave her be?
- This is bad.
- What's "Senior Secretary"?
It's fine. We're leaving tomorrow.
- You guys go and get ready.
- Where's my coat? Bring my coat!
- Give me that.
- Boss.
- I can…
- Coming!
As you know, there are three floors
with 121 shops in our apartment complex.
This way, sir.
Gosh.
Congratulations on becoming
the residents' association president!
- Congratulations!
I'm True Value State's new president,
Park Hae-kang.
Nice to meet you all.
Applause!
We look forward to working with you.
This is our merchants' association
membership list.
If you visit any of our shops
and tell us you're the president,
everything will be on the house.
On the house? Why?
Because you're the president.
That includes your family too.
Our president doesn't accept
bribes of any kind.
- Let's go.
- Right.
Our president is here.
Everyone,
as his Senior Secretary for Civil Affairs,
let me make an important announcement.
President Park will not accept
bribes of any kind.
Take back everything you brought.
Take them back.
We look forward to working with you,
President Park!
Let's go, True Value!
Sir.
Here.
For your hard work.
What is this?
Take that
and announce that all the relics
found here were fabricated.
Relics like this
can't have been discovered here.
You really…
are quick-witted.
You understood right away.
Make an announcement
with what you just said.
No, I'm serious. It's almost impossible
for such relics to be found here.
What?
The soil on the relics doesn't match,
and they're all from different periods.
They can't have been found like this
unless someone planted them here.
So someone planted them on purpose?
If I catch whoever did this,
I'm going to kill them.
- Hello?
- Hey, cop.
You got the call from Mr. Song, right?
I need some help from you.
I LOVE YOU, RU-I
Gyeong-buk.
Ha-ri, what are you doing here?
I just made a parking account
with the benefits of a checking account
and a savings account.
Right. You can make deposits
and withdrawals with daily interest.
- I heard about it.
- Yeah, that one.
A savings plan felt like too much,
so this was perfect for me.
I should make one too.
I really wanted this plushie.
Hey. Just take it.
You can make one online too.
- Really?
- Look.
Hello?
This is True Value Kindergarten.
Is this Gyeong-buk's mom?
You've got the wrong number.
Wait! Hello?
Yes, I'm Gyeong-buk's mom.
You're his kindergarten teacher.
PRESIDENT PARK HAE-KANG
You must be exhausted from all that work,
President Park.
Here, drink this.
Here. Cheers.
Mr. Park, there's an emergency…
Gosh.
Ma'am, you should be careful
of how you address him in public.
Did you just call him "Mr. Park"?
You're married, you know.
- Honey.
- Yes, dear?
Gyeong-buk's having a sports day today.
All the other parents are playing games,
but we're the only ones absent.
Do you have something to say?
That's what he was trying to say
this morning. Let's go.
Goodness. What are you doing?
President Park,
you have a huge pile of work to do.
You can't go.
Ma'am, mothers should
take care of such matters.
Why should I go alone?
He has a father too.
For a man to achieve great things,
his family needs to make some sacrifices.
Ms. Jang.
Would events held by the kindergarten
mostly be attended
- by parents of True Value?
- Of course.
Then I'd say this is the perfect chance
to solidify my position as the president
and build the image of a loving father.
What do you think, Ms. Jang?
Then I'll clear out your entire afternoon.
Wait for me!
Riding the waves with Mom and Dad!
Ready, go!
Go, Team Pink! Go, Team Blue!
Go, Team Pink!
Go! Look at Team Pink!
Team Pink wins!
Team Pink won! Your team won, Gyeong-buk!
- Let's do it together next.
- No.
Why? Come on. Let's do it together.
Everyone, True Value's
President Park Hae-kang is here.
He's Gyeong-buk's father.
I'm Park Hae-kang.
Gyeong-buk!
- They do kind of look alike.
- So he's his son.
How did you know?
I know everything.
Gyeong-buk, why didn't you tell us
today was Sports Day?
This isn't some huge secret.
Because we're not a real family.
I'll show you that I can do even better
since I'm not real.
They're all dead.
I'm going to defeat
all the mothers here today!
Let's win!
EXPANDABLE LUGGAGE BAGS
- Sir.
- What are you looking for?
Are these all the bags you have?
They're smaller than I thought.
Small?
You have no idea.
They can expand like magic.
You can fit ten billion in cash.
Then I'll need at least two.
What? You have 20 billion?
I wish. How much is it?
- Let's go eat, everyone.
- Yes, sir.
Geez. Why isn't this working?
This is driving me crazy.
- Hello.
- You're the president's brother.
He's not here right now, though.
Can I help you?
Oh, he's not here.
I thought we could have lunch…
Is that broken?
Thank you!
I would've gotten scolded again
if it weren't for you.
Is this for a meeting?
It's our business plan for this year.
The president changed,
so we need a new one.
I didn't mean I'm unhappy
that the president changed.
Should I put this on his desk?
You're really kind, unlike how you look.
Is there anything else I can help with?
You can ask me anything.
Excuse me.
Are you Mr. Used Goods Fairy?
- You're Mr. No Discount?
- Yes.
The rice cooker…
- The rice cooker.
- Yes.
- Here.
- Right.
- It works well.
- Okay.
- No refunds or exchanges.
Here.
Thank you for the discount,
Mr. Used Goods Fairy.
Please write a good review.
A round of applause
for Gyeong-buk's father's kick!
Go!
Go, Mom! Go!
It's neck and neck!
Gyeong-buk's mother is in first place!
Gyeong-buk's mother wins!
With more energy!
Don't hesitate! Dance with more energy!
Today's highlight.
This game will be a four-legged race
to demonstrate family unity.
Children from the winning teams
will get to choose their own reward.
You'll start at the sound of the whistle.
Ready…
Go!
- Go!
Park Hae-kang!
Oh my gosh.
Ms. Kang, get up.
Help me.
Sorry, Gyeong-buk.
Are you okay?
Go!
President Park!
Beef! Ginseng!
We can't give up. Let's go!
Let's go.
- There you go!
- We can do it!
The team in first place
chose the ginseng set.
What will you choose, Gyeong-buk?
Beef.
Choose the beef.
The beef.
The hair roller set.
I want this one.
Gyeong-buk.
Why would you…
There are lots of other great gifts.
Why that one?
I saw on TV that other moms all have this,
but my mom, Kang Ha-ri,
doesn't seem to have one.
- What a good son.
- So admirable.
Sons are the best.
Goodness. What a good son.
You're such a great son.
You were worried about my hair. Let's see.
There are different kinds of hair rollers.
This is much better than beef.
Thank you, Gyeong-buk.
Our Gyeong-buk
is so considerate, isn't he?
Give our kind Gyeong-buk
a round of applause!
Yes, let's give a round of applause.
I'm so happy.
He chose hair rollers
over beef and ginseng.
Does Gyeong-buk like me that much?
How do I look? Pretty?
What kind of reaction is that?
I'll give my bangs some volume
before coming to work tomorrow.
Boss, everything's done.
Ms. Kang.
Yes?
You don't have to come to work anymore.
What? What do you mean?
It hasn't been two weeks yet.
You don't have to fill the two weeks.
I'll transfer the money to you by today.
Great work. You can go now.
You're just sending me off right now?
- My bag is still there--
- I'll have your things delivered to you.
Take a cab home.
Goodbye then.
What?
Isn't that ridiculous?
How could he do this?
How can he just treat me like this
after all the time we spent together?
Was that all just a lie?
Yeah.
Of course it was.
It was a stand-in service.
Still…
How could he just send me away
so coldly like that?
Forget it.
You got the rest of the payment.
You should focus on your studies now.
I will, but…
I just feel so upset.
- Boss.
- Yes?
- Here.
- Right.
Good job.
You all did great.
We just have to drop by the bank
tomorrow morning and leave.
What about Gyeong-nam?
He went to take Gyeong-buk back.
But sir, what about Ms. Kang?
- It's done.
- What?
You don't need to worry about it.
We didn't even get to say goodbye to her.
It's really stretchy.
Looks yummy.
- Eat up.
- Okay.
It's good.
- Is it? Eat as much as you want.
- Yes.
Gyeong-buk.
It was tough living in Seoul, wasn't it?
What do you mean?
I mean, there were lots of people at home.
Even a weird grandpa.
You suddenly had a mom and several uncles.
And I made you lie
and call Uncle Hae-kang your dad.
No.
I was happy to have Mom, my uncles,
and Grandpa there.
I want to do it again.
I think I like having a family, Dad.
We'll be a family again next time.
Okay. Promise?
I saw it. There's no need to hide it.
You really should quit gambling now, sir.
Mr. Park.
Did you just…
speak politely to me?
You're not young anymore.
Are you going to keep living like this?
You're scaring me, Mr. Park.
Did I do something wrong again?
Don't kill me. You said you'd let me live.
It's not that. Just sit comfortably.
Come on.
You did a great job.
I'll cancel the debt you owe
to our gambling den.
Mr. Park.
So you got everything.
Is tomorrow the big day?
Once we drop by the bank tomorrow
and get the money,
I'll give you a portion.
No, Mr. Park.
It's fine. I'm really fine.
I'm already grateful
that you let me stay and hide here.
Are you sure?
Yes. I'm really okay.
Live a decent life now.
I will.
You know I have contacts
everywhere, right?
If I ever hear that you're gambling again,
then I'll really cut off your hands.
Get some sleep.
He's…
really thoughtful.
How handsome.
We'll hit the bank in the morning,
get the money, send it to Mr. Son,
then leave Seoul.
I found an island
where we can lie low for a while.
- And the Lizard?
- I told him to go to our car.
Let's start over
after we get Yong-man back.
- Yes, Boss.
Let's go.
How may I help you?
I'd like to withdraw
the entire amount in cash.
- The entire amount?
- Yes.
Do you live in an apartment?
- Then you'd know.
We have some major construction coming up.
I'm the residents' association president.
As you know,
it costs a fortune to replace an elevator.
- Should I give you this bag?
- No, it's fine.
- Just a moment.
- All right.
What is this?
You wanted the entire amount.
It's 2,530 won.
I want to withdraw everything.
Your balance is 7,280 won.
He's taking a long time.
Is it too heavy to carry on his own?
Here's your 7,650 won.
Here's your full balance. 4,910 won.
Of course, it's heavy.
Should we have gone with him?
The money is in different banks,
so obviously, it'll take a while.
Here's your total of 9,220 won.
MIRAE BANK
This can't be true.
The long-term repair reserve fund?
There's 17,857,420,000 won.
They said it was there. Where is it?
I went through so much for that money.
I'm Candidate 3 for District 4,
Park Hae-kang!
I'll take care of this problem!
So dig.
- Park Hae-kang!
Move Exit 3 to True Value!
I worked so hard for this.
The 17,857,420,000 won…
Where is my money?
My 17,857,420,000 won!
Where is it?
Mr. Park! Please let me out!
I'm going to suffocate to death!
Please!
Please…
I'm claustrophobic.
Why are we on the roof again?
I'm scared of heights too!
The money isn't there!
The 17,857,420,000 won.
It's not there. Why?
I'm frustrated too.
We all heard it over the phone that day.
She said they had 17.8 billion.
You should be looking
for the one who took it
instead of taking it out on me.
Fine. Then how do we find this person?
Who do you think took it?
It's a huge amount.
Unless the president, facility manager,
and the accountant worked together…
So they took it together?
I just mean it's not certain,
but it's a possibility.
- Zip it up.
- You little…
Wait!
I'm a professional in this field!
How would you get it without me?
What do we do now, Boss?
We need to find it.
I need my money!
But if they really did take it,
how would we find it?
Well, first…
Let's look into those three.
All right then.
It's going to take a while.
Boss, you have to maintain
your position as the president
to make the investigation easier.
Then we'll have to continue
the intermittent family act.
I CAN DO IT!
Read the textbook and follow along.
Unfair dismissal is clearly defined
in Article 23, Paragraph 1
of the Labor Standards Act.
Simply put,
it's a dismissal without a valid reason.
Right. This is an unfair dismissal.
That's why I felt so angry.
Why didn't I think
of the Labor Standards Act?
I should've protested by citing it.
This is all because I didn't study enough.
I should focus on studying.
Why am I using this right now?
Well, kids are innocent.
Gyeong-buk is innocent.
I brought your things.
Let's talk for a moment.
What? He's in front of my house right now?
CIVIL LAW KEY POINTS
What's going on?
Did you change your job
to an express delivery guy?
How have you been?
What kind of greeting is that?
We saw each other yesterday.
We didn't see each other this morning.
I came in person
because I had something to tell you.
Good. I have something to say too.
Article 23, Paragraph 1
of the Labor Standards Act
states that an employer
shall not dismiss an employee
without justifiable cause.
What's the reason for my dismissal?
I made a mistake.
We still need you, Ms. Kang.
Please come back to work.
What?
You fired me yesterday,
and now you want me to come back?
I'm sorry.
You must be quite upset.
I promise to compensate you for--
Excuse me, Mr. Park.
I do like money,
but don't try to solve everything
with your money.
You should be apologizing
and reflecting
for firing someone like that.
I apologize, Ms. Kang.
I am sincerely sorry
if I upset you.
Please work for two more weeks.
It would be harsh to ignore you
when you're begging me like this.
I'll work for two more weeks
as I promised.
Thank you.
Whose car is that?
I think it's an employee's.
Hello, everyone.
Please, sit.
You got all the security footage,
didn't you?
Yes.
Did you find anything interesting?
Among the cars
entering and leaving Oman New Town,
there's one car going in and out
besides the construction vehicles.
We're looking into it now.
Really?
Then we'll find out who that jerk is soon.
President Park.
Hello, Mr. Choi.
What brings you here so early?
And you're here alone
without your family today.
I couldn't sleep all night
thinking about how to run this place,
so I just came to work early.
You were thinking about that all night?
Mr. Choi.
What's the most urgent issue
in our apartment complex right now?
Well, there's the elevator repair issue.
- Elevator repair?
- Yes.
How do we pay for that?
With the reserve fund.
- The long-term repair reserve fund?
- Yes.
It would cost quite a lot.
Will there be any issues using the fund?
Not at all.
This is exactly
what the reserve fund is for.
But the elevator's been
breaking down quite often,
so the repair company
agreed to fix it for free this time.
So when we need to use the reserve fund,
I stamp it as the president,
then you stamp it,
and the accounting manager
processes the payment?
Yes, that's right.
When Ha-jeong returns, I mean.
- Ha-jeong? The accounting manager?
- Yes.
Come to think of it, I've never met her.
Well, Ha-jeong went on vacation
for the first time in years.
She'll be returning soon.
Her desk is over there.
- I see. "Kang Ha-jeong."
- Yes.
She's right there below me
on the organizational chart.
ACCOUNTING MANAGER
KANG HA-JEONG
I'd love to meet her soon.
He skipped work
after he was just elected president.
Did he come to work on time today?
You cut open Gyeong-buk's piggy bank?
Gyeong-nam, stop.
Don't get blood on your hands.
Just like this.
I'll cut him open exactly the same way
and go to jail.
- Move.
- Seriously?
Stop it.
To be honest, I needed some money.
This place…
is actually a gambling den.
A few old folks
are playing gambling games,
but they're terrible at them.
I can easily earn money here.
Shut that mouth.
Hey, stop. Someone might see.
Right, Father. So…
Were you trying to gamble again?
Do you want your hands cut off?
Go home.
My gosh.
Those jerks.
How could they threaten their dad,
even if he has a gambling problem?
That is unforgivable, seriously.
Mom!
Here. Take this.
I just found it.
My dad told me
I shouldn't eat stuff lying around.
Hey, don't you get what I mean?
I like you.
I only like my mom, Kang Ha-ri.
Bye, Gyeong-buk.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
- I don't know.
- Did you fight?
- What?
- Why do you look so upset?
- Did you eat a lot for lunch?
- Mom!
Mom!
So Hye-jun said she liked you,
but you rejected her?
Why? Is she not pretty?
I like you the most, Mom.
You're the prettiest.
Oh my gosh.
You're so silly.
But Gyeong-buk,
I really can't get used to this.
Can't you just call me Ha-ri
when no one's around?
It's so awkward when you call me Mom.
- Can you do that for me?
- Okay, Ha-ri.
I'll buy you chocolate milk.
- Yes!
What the heck did I just hear?
"Ha-ri"?
He called her by her first name?
It's so sweet, Mom.
"Ha-ri."
It's so sweet, Ha-ri.
It's tasty, right?
Ha-ri.
Ha-jeong, what are you doing here?
What about you?
Who is that, Mom?
"Mom"?
Well, it's…
It's so strange.
Do you want your hands cut off?
The way those jerks spoke to their father…
Can't you just call me Ha-ri
when no one's around?
And she told him to call her
by her first name.
Whatever. Forget it.
It's not my business.
Right.
What family doesn't have problems?
Right. Every family does.
But still…
It's the president's family.
The president's family
shouldn't have issues like that.
- Dad, the elevator's broken.
- It's broken?
Mr. Park, let me talk to you for a second.
What is it?
We looked into the owner of that car, sir.
What? It's Park Hae-kang.
It's the only one
besides the construction vehicles
and the cars whose owners
we've identified.
Then does that mean
Park Hae-kang planted them
to raise housing prices
and get elected as the president?
Yes, it seems so.
Wow.
President Park Hae-kang…
He's quite something.
Mr. Park, I'm sorry,
but I can't work here anymore.
What do you mean?
Something came up.
You can't just quit like this.
You fired me suddenly too.
So just consider us even now.
You already received your payment.
You should do your job.
You said you're a professional.
Even a professional
can have an emergency sometimes!
What is that emergency? Let me hear it.
I can't tell you.
What's the point in being your wife
for two more weeks?
You already got the position
that you wanted so badly.
Our family still needs you, Ms. Kang.
Mr. Park, that family you speak of
is fake anyway!
What?
"Fake"?
Oh my goodness. You…
So you guys
were a fake family?
THE APARTMENT JOB
Emptying out the entire account
makes no sense.
Make something that requires you
to use the fund.
- Let's find…
- Defects!
Since it's an emergency,
I'll allow a wide range of touching.
I can tell that you're faking it.
- Ms. Jang!
He would've found out
that the account is empty.
The reserve fund. He became the president
to pocket the fund.
We don't have time.
Find anything that can be paid for
out of the reserve fund.
Precisely 123 households
have a heating bill of zero.
President Park.
Then will you become
another Heating Bill Martyr?
Heating Bill Martyr…
I don't get how Park found out.
I won't let it happen again--
I'm enjoying this,
so just let Park Hae-kang
do what he wants.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park